Finding Aid for Michigan Bell Telephone Company Photographs 1949-1983
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Michigan Bell Telephone Company Photographs
1949-1983
Michigan Bell Telephone Company.
Photographs (positive and negative), slides, and transparencies taken by the company's photographers to document company activities, products, services, employees at work and at leisure, company exhibits and commemorations, and the response of the company to natural disasters and civil disturbances.
94130 Bb.2/2
63 linear feet in 93 boxes
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Michigan Bell Telephone Company (now Ameritech), and came to the library in August 1993 (Donor no. 304 ).
The collection is open for research.
The photographic department of Michigan Bell Telephone Company was established to document the activities of the company and to provide images to be used in various company publications and publicity releases.
In 1993, Michigan Bell as a corporate entity was subsumed within the Ameritech Corporation. As a by-product of this reorganization and the downsizing resulting from it, the company agreed to deposit with the Bentley Historical Library its extensive archive of photographic images. Totalling approximately one million images, the Michigan Bell Telephone Company photo archive consists of negatives, copy prints, and color transparencies taken in the period since World War II (the bulk beginning in 1949). The collection does not include photos taken since 1983; interspersed throughout, however, are numerous images from before 1949.
The collection has been maintained in the order received with two principal series: Positives and Negatives.
The content of the photographs in the two series varies considerably. Naturally the collection documents the products of the company (phones and other communication devices) and the services provided (e.g. employees at work or the company reacting to a specific customer need). These photos were taken both to inform the general public as accompaniment to press notices and advertising copy and as a communications vehicle within the company, informing employees through the company news publication, Tielines, of activities going on in other divisions of the company or among the various regional Bell offices.
More importantly perhaps, the collection has value for its documentation of events and activities that are common to all large companies. These include images relating to: 1. The activities of employees within the corporation at their work (office workers, repairmen, operators, various support personnel, managers, etc.); 2. The activities of employees outside their work routine as members of corporate social groups (i.e., the company baseball or ice hockey team), at home engaged in leisure time activities, or involved in company-sponsored charitable or public service functions; and 3. Commemorations of specific milestones or events (company parade floats, area office open houses, corporate displays at public events such as fairs, etc.).
In addition, the collection documents the extraordinary and unforeseen as the phone company reacts to events and emergencies not within its control (floods, tornadoes, fires, the 1967 Detroit riot, strikes, and the like) or as a participant in history-making events (the announcement in Ann Arbor of the success of the Salk polio vaccine or the preparation involved in the 1980 Republican National Convention that convened in Detroit).
Subjects - Visual Material:
Accidents.; Adult education.; African Americans.; Aged persons.; Agriculture.; Air defenses.; Air pollution.; Airports.; Allen Park (Mich.); Ambassador Bridge (Detroit, Mich. and Windsor, Ont.); American Red Cross.; American Telephone and Telegraph Company.; Anchor Bay (Mich.); Animals.; Archives.; Artificial larynx.; Artificial satellites.; Automobiles.; Automobile industry.; Autumn.; Bald, F. Clever (Frederick Clever), 1897-1970.; Baseball.; Basketball.; Battle Creek (Mich.); Bay City (Mich.); Beauty contestants.; Bell, Alexander Graham, 1847-1922.; Bell Telephone Laboratories, inc.; Bell Telephone hour (Radio program); Birmingham (Mich.); Blood donations.; Blue Water Bridge (Port Huron, Mich. and Sarnia, Ont.); Boats.; Bowling.; Boy Scouts of America.; Bridges--Michigan.; Britannia (Yacht); Broadcasting.; Buildings.; Buildings--Michigan--Detroit.; Buildings--Michigan--Southfield.; Business and finance.; Business enterprises.; Cables.; Cadillac (Mich.); Cadillac Building (Detroit, Mich.); Cafeterias.; Calder, Alexander, 1898-1976.; Camping.; Cathode ray tubes.; Centennial celebrations.; Chickens.; Children.; Children singing.; Children's parties.; Chris-Craft Industries.; Celebrations.; Christmas.; Christmas decorations.; Churches.; Civil defense.; Cobo Hall (Detroit, Mich.); Coins--Collectors and collecting.; Community service.; Compressors.; Computers.; Confectioners.; Construction industry--Michigan--Detroit.; Cookery.; Country life.; Curling.; Customer relations.; Customs inspections.; Detroit Builder's Show.; Detroit (Mich.)--Buildings, structures, etc.; Civic Center (Detroit, Mich.); Detroit Historical Museum.; Detroit Institute of Arts.; Detroit Metro Airport.; Detroit News (Firm). Want Ads Dept.; Detroit River (Mich. and Ont.); Detroit (Mich.)--Streets.; Detroit Tigers (Baseball team); Detroit (Mich.); Detroit Zoological Park (Mich.); DEW Line.; Diesel electric power-plants.; Dining rooms.; Disasters.; Display of merchandise.; Dolls.; Dwellings--Michigan--Allen Park.; Dwellings--Michigan--Inkster.; Engines.; Engineering.; Equipment.; Excavation.; Exhibitions.; Explosions.; Fairs--Michigan.; Families.; Farming.; Farms.; Fashion shows.; Fiber optics.; Fire alarms.; Fires.; First aid in illness and injury.; Fishing--Michigan.; Flat Rock (Mich.); Flint (Mich.); Flint journal.; Floods.; Flowers.; Food.; Football.; Ford Motor Company.; Fort Custer (Mich.); Fort Wayne (Detroit, Mich.); 4-H clubs.; Frankenmuth (Mich.); Fred Sanders (Firm); Furniture.; Garroway, Dave, 1913-1982.; General Motors Corporation.; General Motors Corporation. Buick Motor Division.; Girl Scouts of the United States of America.; Golf.; Goodwill Industries of America.; Grand Marais (Mich.); Grand Rapids (Mich.); Grocery stores.; Grosse Ile Naval Air Station (Mich.); Handicapped persons.; Health care.; Hearing aids.; Henry Ford Museum and Greenfield Village.; Hillsdale (Mich.); Hobbies.; Holland (Mich.); Horner Woolen Company.; Horseback riding.; Horses.; Hospitals--Michigan--Battle Creek.; Hotels and taverns.; Houghton (Mich.); Hudsonville (Mich.); Hunting--Michigan.; Hurricanes.; Hyatt Regency Dearborn.; Iceboating.; Ice hockey.; Inkster (Mich.); Ionia (Mich.); Janitors.; Junior Achievement.; Kalamazoo (Mich.); Kappel, Frederick R., 1902-; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963.; Kitchens.; Labor unions.; Laborers.; Lansing (Mich.); Law and legal affairs.; Law offices.; Leisure.; Lighthouses--Michigan.; Lincoln Park (Mich.); Lotteries.; Mackinac Bridge (Mich.); Mackinac, Straits of (Mich.); Mackinaw City (Mich.); Magic.; Manistee (Mich.); Manhole covers.; Marion (Mich.); Medicine--Michigan.; Michigan Bell Building (Detroit, Mich.); Michigan Bell Telephone Company.; Michigan--Capital and capitol.; Michigan. Constitutional Convention (1961-1962); Michigan. National Guard.; Michigan Stadium (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Michigan State Fair.; Michigan State Police.; Michigan State University--Campus.Campus.; Michigan State University--Commencement--1963.1963.Commencement; Michigan Week.; Microwave communication systems.; Military life.; Mobile communication systems.; Mobile homes.; National Bank of Detroit.; National Cherry Festival (Traverse City, Mich.); Newspapers--Michigan.; Nike rocket.; Northland Shopping Center (Southfield, Mich.); Nurses--Michigan.; Oak Park (Mich.); Occupations.; Office equipment.; Office workers.; Offices--Michigan--Detroit.; Parades and processions.; Percy Jones Hospital (Battle Creek, Mich.); Photographers.; Physicians--Michigan.; Pickets.; Pickles.; Pinsetters.; Playboy bunny.; Plymouth (Mich.); Police--Michigan.; Poliomyelitis vaccine.; Political conventions--Michigan--Detroit.; Politicians--Michigan.; Port Huron (Mich.); Printing industry.; Prison facilities--Michigan--Jackson.; Project Telstar.; Publicity.; Racquets (Game); Radar.; Radioisotopes.; Employees--Recruiting.; Refugees--Michigan.; Renaissance Center (Detroit, Mich.); Republican National Convention (32nd: 1980: Detroit, Mich.); Retirement.; Riots.; Riots--Michigan--Detroit--History--20th century.; River Rouge (Mich.); Rockets.; Royal Oak (Mich.); Safety.; Saginaw (Mich.); Sailboats.; Sailing.; Saint Ignace (Mich.); Sales, Soupy.; Salt mining--Michigan.; Schools--Michigan.; Sculpture--Michigan--Detroit.; Seasons.; Selfridge Air National Guard Base (Mich.); Ships--Great Lakes.; Shopping centers.; Signal towers.; Signs.; Singing.; Skiing.; Soap box derbies.; Soda fountains.; Solar batteries.; Southfield (Mich.); Sports.; Square dancing.; Stained glass.; Strikes.; Standale (Mich.); State Prison of Southern Michigan.; Students--Michigan.; Submarine cables.; Storms.; Swimming.; Telephones.; Telephone cables.; Table tennis.; Telephone--Defense measures.; Telephone, Dial.; Telephone directories.; Telephone--Employees.; Telephone lines.; Telephone--Equipment and supplies.; Telephone operators.; Telephone etiquette.; Telephone repeaters.; Telephone switchboards.; Telephone--History.; Telephone switching systems, Electronic.; Telephone systems.; Telephone wire.; Teletypewriters.; Television industry.; Tennis.; Thom, Robert A.; Traffic accidents.; Transistors.; Transportation--Michigan.; Traverse City (Mich.); Trees, Care of.; Tornadoes.; Turbines.; Towers.; Trucks.; Turkeys.; Uniforms.; Universities and colleges--Michigan.; United Foundation (Detroit, Mich.); Vocational education.; Volleyball.; Vorhees, Donald, 1903-1989.; Voting.; WWJ-TV (Television station: Detroit, Mich.); Weddings.; Western Electric Company.; Window displays.; Winter.; Women--Michigan.; Athletes--Michigan.; Women athletes--Michigan.; World War, 1939-1945--War work.; Wurtsmith Air Force Base (Mich.); Wyandotte (Mich.); Youth--Michigan.
Genre/Form:
Advertisements.; Aerial photographs--Michigan--Detroit.; Photographs.; Paintings.
- Positive Photographic Prints
  Arranged alphabetically by topic, the series Positive Photographic Prints consists of more than 700 folders of positive images: mainly contact prints and transparencies, with occasional slides and copy prints. Each image also includes some brief description and the job number. With the job number, the researcher will be able to locate the negative should a copy be requested. To aid the researcher in finding images on a specific subject, an index to this series has been created and appended to this finding aid. As many of the images are of equipment and product development, the researcher should first consult the folder listing as many of the telephone specific headings have not been indexed. The subject index has been geared to subjects of a more general interest (women in the work place, sports, leisure activities, views of Michigan communities, and so forth). The researcher should also note that the Positives series does not include positive images of all of the negatives taken by Michigan Bell photographers. The prints are, however, a good representation of the kinds of photographs taken. It should also be noted that there are prints in this series for which there are no corresponding negatives in the Negatives series. There are occasional negatives in this series filed here by topic because they did not include a job number and thus could not be filed with the rest of the negatives.
  - Accidents - Concentrator switches
    - Accidents (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Accounting personnel, 4 folders (Box 1, Folder 2-5)
    - Activities-Employees, 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - Advertising Club (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Advertising directory (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Advertising-Magic Show (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Agriculture (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Air conditioning unit (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Air defense-Dew Line (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Alarm systems (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Alcoholism and Drugs (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - AMANDA-Automatic telephone answering equipment (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Amplifying equipment (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Animals (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Artificial larynx (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Assessment centers (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Assignment clerks (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - AT & T-Buildings (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - AT & T-Michigan employees (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - AT & T-Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - AT & T-Stockholders meeting (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Audio-visual equipment (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Auditors (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Automatic call distributor (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Automatic Message Accounting (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Automotive industry (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Awards, 3 folders (Box 1, Folder 31-33)
    - Bell, Alexander Graham (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Bell Boy (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Bell Forum (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Bell Labs (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Benefits-Employees (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Benefits-Group Insurance (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Bosco House (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Boy Scouts (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Boats (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Bridges-Michigan (mainly Mackinac Bridge) (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Building Services (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Buildings
      - Detroit
        - Michigan Bell Building
          - 1917-1920 (Box 2, Folder 45)
          - 1940s-1950s (Box 2, Folder 46)
          - 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 47)
          - Aerial (Box 2, Folder 48)
          - Negatives and transparencies (Box 2, Folder 49)
          - 19th & 20th floors-1974 renovation (Box 2, Folder 50)
        - Michigan Bell Building Addition, 1969-1972
          - Models (Box 2, Folder 51)
          - Dedication ceremony, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 52)
          - Construction views, etc., 6 folders (Box 2, Folder 53-58)
          - Exterior, 1972-1982 (Box 2, Folder 59)
          - Interiors (Box 2, Folder 60)
          - Lobby-Christmas exhibit (Box 2, Folder 61)
          - Sculpture-Alexander Calder stabile, 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 62-63)
        - Hyatt Regency (Box 2, Folder 64)
        - Riverfront (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - Southfield-Southfield Center (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - Non-Michigan-Bell and AT & T buildings (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Cable
      - Aerial (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - Breaks-Submarine
        - Bay City (Box 2, Folder 69)
        - Mackinaw City-St. Ignace (Box 2, Folder 70)
      - Buried, 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 71-72)
      - Coaxial (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - Construction (Box 2, Folder 74)
      - Damaged (Box 2, Folder 75)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 76)
      - Pressurization (Box 2, Folder 77)
      - Submarine (Box 2, Folder 78)
      - Testing (Box 2, Folder 79)
      - Underground (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Calculagraphs (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - CAMA equipment (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Camera Club (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Camping (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Card dialer and rapidialer (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Carrier huts "K" and "P" (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Carrier systems (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Cathode ray tube (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Central Offices (also employees plant central office) (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Centrex (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Centrex (DID, DOD, AMA) (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Children and phones (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Children's chorus (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Children's contest (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Christmas decorations, 2 folders (Box 3, Folder 95-95a)
    - Christmas dolls (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Christmas parties and charitable activities, 1947-1975; 5 folders (Box 3, Folder 97-101)
    - Churches (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Cities-Michigan
      - Bay City (Box 3, Folder 103)
      - Dearborn-Greenfield Village (Box 3, Folder 104)
      - Detroit
        - Civic Center (Box 3, Folder 105)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 106)
        - Renaissance Center (Box 3, Folder 107)
      - Flint (Box 3, Folder 108)
      - Grand Rapids (Box 3, Folder 109)
      - Holland (Box 3, Folder 110)
      - Houghton (Box 3, Folder 111)
      - Kalamazoo (Box 3, Folder 112)
      - Lansing (Box 3, Folder 113)
      - Manistee (Box 3, Folder 114)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 115)
      - Saginaw (include negatives) (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Civil Defense (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Coin collectors (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Colleges and universities (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - COMKEY (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Commercial power panel (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Committees (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Community relations (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Competitor's equipment (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Compressor (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Comptroller's operations (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Computer-accounting (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Computers-employees (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Concentrator cable (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Concentrator switches (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Conduits - Employees
    - Conduits (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Construction (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Convention (Republican National Convention, 1980) (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Customer services (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Cut-over dial-St. Ignace (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Damage
      - Explosion-Flat Rock (Box 4, Folder 136)
      - Fire
        - Ann Arbor (Box 4, Folder 137)
        - Briggs Plant (Box 4, Folder 138)
        - General Motors (Box 4, Folder 139)
        - Lansing (Box 4, Folder 140)
        - Oak Park (Lincoln Office Center) (Box 4, Folder 141)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 142)
      - Floods (Box 4, Folder 143)
      - Grade Separation (Box 4, Folder 144)
      - Hurricane-New England (Box 4, Folder 145)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 146)
      - Open Wire Breaks (Box 4, Folder 147)
      - Plant Emergency (Box 4, Folder 148)
      - Storms
        - Bay City (Box 4, Folder 149)
        - Flat Rock (Box 4, Folder 150)
        - Hillsdale (Box 4, Folder 151)
        - Holland (Box 4, Folder 152)
        - Metro North (Box 4, Folder 153)
        - New England (Box 4, Folder 154)
        - Northern Division (Box 4, Folder 155)
        - River Rouge, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 156)
        - Southern Division (Box 4, Folder 157)
      - Tornadoes
        - General (Box 4, Folder 158)
        - Allen Park and Lincoln Park (Box 4, Folder 159)
        - Anchor Bay (Box 4, Folder 160)
        - Flint (Box 4, Folder 161)
        - Grand Rapids & Hillsdale (Box 4, Folder 162)
        - Hudsonville & Standale (Box 4, Folder 163)
        - Port Huron (Box 4, Folder 164)
        - Royal Oak (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Dancing, Square (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - DAS/M operations (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Dataphone (also equipment TWX) (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Data processing (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Dataspeed (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Demonstrations (equipment, training sessions, etc.), 4 folders (Box 4, Folder 171-174)
    - Design Line Phones
      - Color prints (with negatives) (Box 5, Folder 175)
      - Black and white (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Detroit Institute of Arts (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Detroit Metropolitan Airport (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Detroit Renaissance Center-Telephone Exchange Building construction, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Dial equipment (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Dial instructors (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Dial "1" campaign (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Diesel equipment (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Dining services (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Directories, 2 folders (Box 5, Folder 185-186)
    - Directory Assistance Office (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Displaced persons working with the company, 1952; 1957 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Displays
      - Advertising campaign (with Playboy Bunny), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 189)
      - Bell Auditorium (Box 5, Folder 190)
      - Cadillac Building, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 191)
      - Cobo Hall (Box 5, Folder 192)
      - Detroit Builders' Show (Box 5, Folder 193)
      - Detroit Historical Museum (Box 5, Folder 194)
      - Fairs
        - County (Box 5, Folder 195)
        - Little Theaters (Box 5, Folder 196)
        - Michigan State Fair (Box 5, Folder 197)
        - Shopping centers (Box 5, Folder 198)
      - Flowers (Box 5, Folder 199)
      - Miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 5, Folder 200-205)
      - Public Office
        - Bell Building (Box 5, Folder 206)
        - Birmingham (Box 5, Folder 207)
        - Royal Oak (Box 6, Folder 208)
        - Wyandotte (Box 6, Folder 209)
      - Stores (Box 6, Folder 210)
      - Universities (Box 6, Folder 211)
      - Windows
        - Bell addition, 6 folders (Box 6, Folder 212-217)
        - Michigan Bank (Box 6, Folder 218)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 219)
        - Siegel's (slides) (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - DDD Service Bureau (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - Drop wires 1944-1945, 1960, 1966 (include negatives) (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - Eagle Scouts (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Edison poles (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - Elections (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Electric Switching System (ESS) (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - Electronic Secretary (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - Emergency equipment (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - Emergency portable engine (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - Employee activities (non-work, charitable), 1955-1958; 2 folders (Box 6, Folder 230-231)
    - Employee activities (non-work, golf, etc)-Commercial Department (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - Employee activities (non-work, golf, etc)-Engineers (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - Employee activities (non-work, charitable, etc)-Plant Department (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - Employees and employees at work, 2 folders (Box 6, Folder 235-236)
    - Employees-Getting to work (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - Employees-Skilled/craft, 4 folders (Box 6, Folder 238-241)
  - Employment - Hearing aids
    - Employment high school counselors (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Employment Merit brochures (with images of employees at work) (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - Employment Office (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - Employment recruiting
      - General (Box 7, Folder 245)
      - College (Box 7, Folder 246)
      - High school, 2 folders (Box 7, Folder 247-248)
    - Energy conservation (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - Engineering (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - Engineering Customer Division (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - Engineering real estate (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Environmental protection (includes examples of air pollution) (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Equal employment opportunity (includes photos of women and African Americans) (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Equipment
      - Damaged (Box 7, Folder 255)
      - Data Phone (Box 7, Folder 256)
      - DMS 100 (Box 7, Folder 257)
      - Donated (Box 7, Folder 258)
      - Installation
        - Detroit News Want Ads department, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 259)
        - Federal Telecommunications System (Box 7, Folder 260)
        - Gas Company (Box 7, Folder 261)
        - Miscellaneous and odd locations (Box 7, Folder 262)
        - National Bank of Detroit (Box 7, Folder 263)
        - Outside companies (Box 7, Folder 264)
        - Rapidial (Box 7, Folder 265)
        - Telephones on trains, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 266)
        - Telephones in motels and hotels (Box 7, Folder 267)
      - Instruments
        - Illustrations (Box 7, Folder 268)
        - Miscellaneous, 9 folders (Box 7, Folder 269-277)
        - Modern (Box 7, Folder 278)
        - Modern (telephone usage) (Box 7, Folder 279)
      - Parts of a telephone (Box 8, Folder 280)
      - Testing apparatus (Box 8, Folder 281)
      - Ticket holder (Box 8, Folder 282)
    - Explorer scouts (Box 8, Folder 283)
    - Fairs (Box 8, Folder 284)
    - Family life (Box 8, Folder 285)
    - Farms-Chicken hatchery (Box 8, Folder 286)
    - Fashion (Box 8, Folder 287)
    - Fiber optics (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - Films Bell System (Box 8, Folder 289)